All the Brown Army of MI BL Brown
Munde on the field Already we are waiting for
the moment for the final match Who will lift the
trophy Who will lift the
cup on Dazzlers' two opening batsmen be
present as soon as possible
So here we go
Keeping the bat aside we will strike with the sword
Will he send it across the boundary line The
thunder has already been heard Let's start
So coming up final
match MI BL And here we have the two opening
batsmen
Two teams for one cup
ok let's play We will have count down
from 10
Now so here we go Everyone present over Here we will have
the countdown 10 with me Everyone
10 no 8 sen six for four two one Are you
ready let's play Let's roll MI BL final
match First ball Captain Rahul Panchal
and the wicket has fallen on the first ball What a
fantastic start Absolutely he got out on the first ball
Absolutely start MI BL Brown
Munde The final match has got a great start And he got it done
on the first ball
So these two teams will now face each other for a cup.
Welcome back once again to the finals of
ICC Lombard Brokers Premier League
2025. N Dazzlers vs MI
IBL. The patient needs medicine and when Jogi
needs it. The patient needs medicine and when Jogi needs it.
We are the worshippers of cricket. When do we need this
tournament?
Make some noise and let's start.
First
ball. First wicket.
Siddesh par ab
batsman so on the first ball the captain was
out. Big wicket fell here in a
jiffy. Very good stop shut fine leg
so five balls bowled six for one. N
Dazzlers played defensively. Good start.
Arshad Ansari after one over six for one air
Dazzlers
not over six for
one final match eight over game
A Dazzlers MI
PL to not the gap will go for the
second boundary of the
match. Previous over first boundary from
Siddhesh Chauhan one on one 10 A Dazzlers
score no the fielder played d point
region for single
run one on two 11 A Dazzlers
Good turn read here and pushed it
stole a run Siddhesh More no
pv final match in
progress toss win by a elected to bat
set up the big total how will they challenge MI
BL short pizzy ball very well play the
fielder rat s will come back for
two very good throw excellent throw only a
single
run one the ch 1 pv
n dazzlers MB
good performance in the
semi final now two big contenders who will win who will
lose one dash pv 14 pv The last ball of this over will be bowled
by Sandeep Salim so the over will end with a dot ball
after two overs 14 pv n dazzlers
after the end of two overs 14 pv n
dazzlers has played two runs at square leg
good running button wicket with speed
got two runs with speed
2 pv 16
pv waiting for hitting for six four
just two boundaries now.  Fav
played defensively this time, he got no runs
Good bowling Harshad
Ansari Very well played towards the deep X
Kaa
Stho single
run at 2.31 An N
Dazzles Mitesh Chauhan and Siddhesh More are batting Mithesh and Siddhesh are
going on a flight Mitesh
and Siddhesh let's send the ball on some flight
Waiting for something special in the
final
match Very good bowling This is excellent
bowling MIPL we saw in the semi-final
now performing well in the final at
2.41 A good start MIBL team
Excellent fielding looking for couple of runs
Only a single run Good fielding by MBL
team Two Dash Pa at 18 An A Dazzles
Excellent bowling Harshad Ansari Two overs 10 runs
One wicket Good bowling Three overs over Game over
at 18 An N
Dazzles Siddhesh More Mitesh
Chauhan waiting for their
fireworks Silence before storm
Umpire raises his finger He's
gone What so
second wicket fall An Dazzles in trouble
now so cut  Behind good work by the wicketkeeper
Akash Su Mitesh Yohan departed from the ball with two fours after
hitting a boundary
.  Two for 22 Now
the new batsman Ranjit Katak
Only a single
run MI BA is something special unit
Fielding unit very
strong Everyone has been
silenced 3.3 Two for 24
Excellent bowling Excellent turn
Only a
single 3.4 Two for 24 N Dazzlers
Very good fielding performance
all around Absolutely this is something
special MI
IBL 3.5 Two for 25
Excellent bowling Quick and good
turn Four overs game over Two for 25 A lot
Four overs
Two for 25 Now something different has to be done here
Siddhesh More and Ranjit Katak will not sit quiet in the coming four overs Need some
fireworks
Need some cracking
hits MI BL Now let's see Praful now into
the
attack Rajit not on strike Takes temp
keeper misses to
collect wide plus one run Two extra
runs Four overs Two for 27 It's
time to become heroes Now N Dazzlers
You can do it Come on
what a fielding  Performance
Absolute excellent fielding set by the
captain 4.128 p.m. IBL captain
Akash Lanjekar has a
good fielding set and has made a good start
in this final match, he tried to take the
catch, he lost something there balance and a reason
catch has been dropped good effort there getting a
lifeline
couple of fours taken couple of fours taken by
Ranjit 4 at 30 p.m. two on dazzles
so very good
bowling it's a dot
ball 4.3 342 n
dazzles it screen ball
namko kart
bowling absolute electrifying and
athletic bowling performance Raful
Navali 4.4 30 three n dazzlers has
completely silenced the crowd here
MBL's Brown Munde all around
four
new ball coming on,
cracking hitter will go, Dave lets see no, he will not let
this go, he ran
three runs here
one run saved for the team three runs taken for  The
team 4.5 33 runs for the loss of three wickets N
Diesels Siddhesh
More 12 for 13 balls A four
Good
bowling Some different
style Good mix and eight runs
Praful managed to take a wicket Five
overs end 33 Fth A Diesels
Sandeep Patil comes into the attack Five overs 33
Fth Three more overs
left The night is still to be discussed Some big hits are
awaited here
Good bowling into the block
hole Excellent
performance 5.13
Fth Outside
edge Fielders are visible everywhere
5 D two 34 for three A
Diesels Just a single Good stop Praling
on past three Dash three 35 for three Good fielding
performance MI BL Brown Army all around A
little bit of a slight hit outside leg
stump and wide signaled
by the umpire Not out at 36
N
Diesels Excellent catches Catch the
match and wickets fall Attempts to hit big shots have
completely ruined the
Brown Army are heavier than brown bread
5.4  36 for
four A good start A
good fielding unit has completely
destroyed the N Dazzlers New batsman
Praneeth Parab will play a special innings and do some
fireworks
5.4 36 f fo Now Praneeth Param the new batsman Only a
single Just four runs in this over
Sandeep
Patil last ball Sixth
over What a
bowling pin drop Silence in the N Dazzlers
dug out Six overs over S Pachar N
Dazzlers
what a thing they won't let go They wo
n't
leave any boundary Absolutely good fielding
performance here Kakan
region A fad takes a catch The Dazzlers batsmen are talking
all around These fielders, fielders what should we
do What is my fault in this
What is the
fault of the team 6.1 39 f four And now wickets are lying
Five wickets
so 395
6.2 Here MI BL have completely
disturbed the batting unit
What have they done and
why
They will answer for this and will say all this
hard work  When will we wait for the final match is on N
Dezellus
MIBL There is
fear of MBL all around
6.3 445
Need Munster looking for the big one Late C Na
Siddhesh
Mori Inside edge Batsman narrowly escapes
Just one run It
's a different set formula MI BL
team Only a single
run 6.5 42 on Pa A on
Dezellus There is no answer to them There is no solution to them
They have no mode And further you complete something
Only a single Walking
single They have no mode There is no mode ahead
End of the over 7 overs 4345 N
Dezellus Very good bowling Only 6
runs Now coming up the final over of the first
innings is here
Labad Procus Premier League
2025 final match is
on Final match on
and fielding is
full on 7 overs 435 Last over now of the
first swing don't
miss Excellent bowling performance
7.1
4345 Stopped back I do
n't know how many bus stops MI
BL has made
today They keep stopping them, they keep stopping them, they keep
making speed breakers  He is making a bus stop
Superb excellent Fanta Bulls
outstanding 45 7 last
ball This is what he was looking for This is what he was waiting for
Siddhesh More strikes for six runs The
lion inside him has awakened now So
with this he is trying to complete 50 runs Once again
strong bat for both the teams Very
well played What a match What a final
match 7.3 51 F F Tough fight between two big
contenders
Two runs will definitely be taken here
7.4 53 at five n
diesels Now something decent score on the total
is looking
fine May be the defendable score now Last
two balls coming
up Went for a big shot But only a
couple of runs Will the
rocket be weak in the last ball Will he
hit a six in the last ball To
know watch the final match of ICC
Lombard Rokus Premier
League So coming up
now let's go for the last ball First innings Here we go
make some noise There are
fielders all around
and he has finally
dismissed Siddhesh More Excellent Once again strong  Taliya
for MI BL
Good fielding performance also make some
noise for A LS has done good batting
So
with this the first innings
ends So after 8 overs
C is 56 and the target is 57 to chase MI BL in
48 balls 8 overs we get a short break
We will be back soon
In the game of life Stay
protected with ICICI Lord Health
Insurance
Jump fooding
ch energy
lo In the game of life Stay protected with
ICICI Lord Health Insurance Power O
[Music]
In the game of life Stay protected with
ICICI Lord Health Insurance
Jumfoor
Ag In the game of life Stay protected with
CC Lombard Health Insurance Power
Restore
[Music]
So with me
everyone three to one let's play hardball
Let's make some noise Come on there and there
people four
people First ball
Captain Rahul Panchal
So now the captain to Captain Rahul Panchal to
Akash There was a chance here but only a single run We will
give something different Tough fight A must see N
LS M
IBL both batsmen are off the mark with a single run,
two balls run, no wicket,
target is 57, first two overs power play, just
two feeders outside
circle, lightly cut and pushed, one run
stolen,
two feeders outside circle, one is mid
wicket and one is Lagan,
good
bowling, will give some tough fight, you will have to watch,
N
Diesels, final game, there is pressure,
pressure,
played it lightly at mid
wicket, only a single,
so good start, we can from N Diesels,
captain taking the charge, Rahul
Panchal, one over, five runs, no wicket,
MBL needs 52 runs, now 42
balls to come, Siddhesh More comes to bowl,
28, 24 balls, ako a
si, now they have to do something amazing, to take wickets, will they be
successful or not or will
Harshad and Akash of MI BL show some different magic,
so here it is the turn of A and Diesels,
fielding has given a
good start, only five runs have been
given in the first over, MI at
1.16 for no
loss, good fielding, good flank shot,
played it at swerve leg and this  Good
technique ME BL
B I don't want to take any risk I will
play in the gap I will understand I will read and then
break the point A F No loss MI B
Both the batsman playing four of four
Akash and
Ansari takes a cracking shot he will get one bounce into the
fence F Four runs
Mumbai City there the cooker whistle rang
excellent shot outside off seamer F
Four Akash Lanjkar
Captain taking the charge
and once again a big connection and what is this
dream broken good effort here what is this
four or
not what a stop
B good stop there only two runs 1.4 14
Fno
Ls Captain completely strong here
Akash Lanjkar has
sent back Simon go back return
ticket 1.51 Fno Ls
and this is an excellent
shot and the catch has been
dropped catch been dropped B
commentator what shot excellent six runs
So in the commentary box what did I miss
and my dream
is broken so what a strike Captain taking the
charge Akash Lanjkar
two overs 20
no wicket and Akash Lanjkar has hit my hand  Has
delivered a
lot of strike rate Batting performance ME
BL Sensible batting these are good batsmen Darshan
Luck Do 21 for no loss 36 Not out get from
5.4 overs Left
single Run taken by
Akash 2.3 22 runs ME
IBL 35 runs 33
Just played in the gap Made room One bounce into the
fence Outside off Rekha This went for
four and has sent it once near Rekha and Seema
Have you got your
insurance done 2.4
26 Excellent batting Harshad and Akash No
wicket yet they will
chase Chasing the target of 57 Just 30 Now to
get 31 balls
Left single to end of the over Excellent
start Three overs 28 No wicket now
29 runs needed in the coming five overs
27 Not out from 26
28 And here
Akash is going for the second
Excellent running between the wickets
back to back
3.32 No
loss Good fielding
given to short extra
cover 25 Runs 26 Gain
and here  Misfield and runs quickly for a run The
captain is batting well Taking the
charge 23 15 ends Arshad Ansari Len with
3.54 no loss
MBL 23 runs from 25
balls Clears the
infield is very good
Stop deep extra
cover Akash The captain has done fireworks today
Four overs over No wicket on 36
Four overs to play 21 to get Will
easily complete this match
After four
36 Cracking shot to like by four
Excellent shot Four runs
Arshad
Ansari striking the well Striking it
straight down the ground
Four 4.1 4 to get No loss 17 to
get Gautam Gokhale The
ball suddenly changed the time Changed the emotions
Changed the life
4.3 42 15 runs
Now lift the cup M IBL
Good effort
and he saved
So good athletic work Fielding done
at t point
region So over ends with a single Five
overs 45 12 runs  Needed in the coming 18 balls
Only 12 required to lift the trophy
of ICCI Lombard Brokers Premier
League 2025 Season 2
5145 Just 12 to hit big to win the
match and will go for
four Harshad Ansari and Akash Lanjekar
Rest of the team members are eating comfortably He is
chilled in gout Both of them are
quite so just a single to get
15 balls left Wide
ball extra run Now needed 7
runs Mahindra Insurance Brokers Ltd
MI BL 50 runs completed
Excellent shot Good fielding
in deep extra cover So one hit away for the
trophy 6 runs keep the shining trophy ready for them
5.4
51 6
runs 14 balls left Can captain finish of
style Will go for white
ball Now fire
required Only a single
now needed 4
runs Will the
batsman hit the ball
across on this ball The over is over So that's the end of
the
over 6 over's play is over 54 Three runs now in
Balls MI BL Mahindra Insurance
Brokers Limited Now to lift the trophy
Just three runs away From
automatic par
point to go
No still silence before stumps
A
storm A big
hit Now the captain is on strike
Need two runs Can he finish off in
style 27 19 W F
S This is sensible They are not in a hurry They have to
lose a wicket They have to make runs And only
one run is
needed now Single run De will win with very
wide and takes it MI BL
The
Champions of ICC Lombard Brokers Premier
League
2025 MI
BL The Champions the OG
This is today's Baazigar Muqaddar ke Sikandar
Excellent congratulations
and very well played
Excellent batting performance Fielding performance
Excellent
performance Congratulations
to MI BL Mahindra Insurance Brokers
Limited
This is today's Baazigar Winner of today's Hero Champions
of ICC Lombard
Brokers Premier League 2025